so a woman recently went viral for begging the question has the megan the stallion challenge
gone too far now you know is amanda seal show so you know i'm not about to spend no three minutes
talking about twerking so just stick around we're going to turn this into an intellectual
combo y'all call it the megan the stallion challenge but to be honest i think it's just
yet another way for women to devalue themselves given society's inclination to police black women's
bodies let's brainstorm some reverse challenges to offer back to society the mind your business
challenge participants must refrain from commenting on or judging the appearance or actions of black
women for an entire week that's seven days bonus points for actively supporting and uplifting black
women instead the empathy walk challenge oh yeah walk a mile in a black woman's shoes by reflecting
on the challenges they face and actively advocating for their rights and autonomy that sounds fun
right yeah but why should black people care
because allowing the culture to police black women's bodies and their tone eventually gives
them a license to dehumanize us so by the way black women that's you too it is very real that we've
grown up in this patriarchal society and oftentimes we find ourselves mimicking it unwittingly so let's
look at ourselves in the mirror and cut it
we are